to there may be a folder,
the team will create a folder name and
they put it in the folder. Okay,
so you guys take that notes automatically
and agent take it and it will run through
it and it will come up with a list of
action items.
So what's the action item is?
the detail, who is the owner,
and the date, if there's a date discussed,
otherwise we have to reach out to the
people and get the dates and an update,
status update, right?
It's in progress and the nodes are is
completed means it will go away. So.
That just to get that and automated and
create that it right now you can do with
your storage table or something this item
but later we can we can move that into my
database.
So,
can we can you guys think got an idea
what I'm looking for?
So is it like an agent that automatically
kind of fetches each transcript after a
meeting and then like sends it to like
the emails of the people who are in the
meeting?
No, no, it is. It creates the action.
There are two parts.
Huh.
The first part is it create all the
action item and store in a database.
Okay, the second one is the one, okay,
you got the action items.
Now there is a owner already.
It sends e-mail to the owner
automatically. Hey,
you got an action item.
This is your action item.
Then it sent a follow up, hey,
have you completed based on because it's
an AI.
right? So it has to check, hey,
what's the status of it?
Does need a follow up or is completed or
something for information.
So based on that,
it will send an e-mail to him again and
or her again. Hey,
these are the things where or where is
what's the status? Then it collect the,
they will respond, right?
So the response come here.
into a notes addendum kind of updating
the database. So we have an interface,
it will show, hey,
they can select the meeting title and it
will show all the action item where they
are, what's the status.
It will automatically update it here.
So that's the whole module.
We wanted to work on.
So you can pick both of you. Okay,
you work on this piece,
you work on the other piece,
then we can integrate, fix cloud, right?
Create a project to share and work on two
pieces separately.
That you both can decide,
but that's what I'm looking for.
First module,
because we have a couple of them like
this, but let's start with that.
This will help everybody's job really
easy. It's very,
Yeah, absolutely.
very useful thing for us to do.
And one more thing I wanted to tell you
guys,
this is this may not be a product
management requirement,
but it is a product management to moving
forward future job going to be like that.
Okay,
so you are going to write your
Yeah.
requirement not in a PR,
the product requirement document or
anything.
You are going to create a prototype and
give it to them,
give it to the engineering, right?
Mhm.
So same thing, same thing you are doing.
It's more like training in terms of your
product management agent.
for SDLC project management.
And I am the engineer developer,
let's put it that way,
you'll be working with,
but I will help you to train and get that
aspect also as a back end.
So this will surely have great exposure
and experience for you guys.
That's what I picked both of you. Okay,
maybe let them do this project because we.
It's all production.
People are all using our system already,
right? I told you.
So that's why I picked this project for
you guys. Yeah.
One question, Hepsi is,
does today does cloud have integration
with Outlook or anything?
Because for the e-mail to be sent out,
right,
we need to have integration with Outlook.
It they have that,
but they said they can enable.
Let's get those all hooked up and running,
and then we will see. Ohh, one more thing.
Where are the bottlenecks?
Let me let me let me give you guys a file.
OK.
But that file is connected to database.
Let me share. Try this file, okay?
That's a starting.
After, yeah, OK.
Yeah, so that's where my,
so he sent a driver first,
and then we saw yesterday, so at last,
okay, at last.
I'm not sure this will work without, okay.
See, I added a file, HTML file.
You guys can,
I'm not sure it will run without some
backend connection.
Why don't you try it out?
This is the one that I am talking about.
something like, let me share also,
let me share that.
I have a module already. Let me share.
Command center I have my you guys have
access to command center, right?
Yeah.
Yes, but for the meeting notes,
it says we need a password to access this
Sorry, yeah, yeah, yeah, so,
so if you go to the main,
paper.
let me see where is commands.
You can.
Whatever.
I have it, I have,
I wanted to go to the home, yeah, so OK,
Which one are you like, like the access?
so this meeting notes, this is what.
Oh, it's not even asking password,
maybe slow.
I think [redacted - portal password].
[redacted - portal password], right?
Yeah, yeah, can you try that? It try,
but why is it not working for me?
No, it says wrong password.
[redacted - portal password].
Yeah.
Then, just [redacted - portal password].
Mhm.
Ohh, it works.
Yeah, [redacted - portal password]. It came out.
Ohh yeah, that's good.
Yeah, okay, so yeah, [redacted - portal password], right? So yeah,
so it's working, right?
[redacted - portal password].
So the way that I did is import
transcript, right?
Yeah.
So they can import transcript.
But I have a transcript somewhere.
Weekly Ops review and transcript.
Meeting node C.I.
Sorry,
I don't know if it's a transcript or
anything. OK, so it will OK, sorry,
this one because it's OK,
you can you have to make it work. OK,
so you can import the transcript.
What it will do is it will extract
everything, the agenda.
The meeting notes and see here if I maybe
I might have something here, right? OK,
see here it's in extracted everything.
Then see here you see here it's created.
Then I also wanted to the action.
I want to send an e-mail and all.
So because it was not if I wanted to do
it manually.
But I want in our case what I'm looking
is if based on the assignee name,
it should automatically send it.
Then it take the notes information and
update here.
Update the notes based on or e-mail send
it to him or emails anything any
transaction happening should be updated
here.
This is the one I shared,
but you have to make the pieces working,
but this is what I'm talking about.
Okay.
And we want all this to be like an
automatic process, right?
Correct, correct. Yes, yes, yes.
I see.
Oh, Hepsi, just a question regarding,
like, who's sending out the emails?
Is it the agent sending out the emails,
or is it on the user's behalf?
Agent, agent, agent. Oh, no,
maybe you can do if possible,
Okay.
whoever the meeting person who organizing
the meeting or the owner of that meeting,
Organizer, organizer.
maybe we can send it from them.
Yeah.
It will be more personal.
Yeah.
Than the agent.
Okay.
Make it as a even the content and
everything,
don't make it as a AI generator. Okay,
so we can say action item from this
meeting. Hi,
you have an action item assigned.
Can you plus check and all like that,
blah blah.
Like a regular normally when you go and
write manually.
How it is, please do that way.
Okay.
But as of now,
our cloud or glean can't like directly
access the teams, right,
to just like pull the transcripts.
So we'd like need that to be done for,
okay, I see.
Yes.
Yeah.
And is that going to be done by now?
How do you talk? I talk, yeah,
or so sorry.
So would that process be done by
engineering or IPT before we kind of kick
I...
start this project or?
Ohh, you write, you write it up,
get the module with the Mokka working,
then what to integrate and all we can
work on it.
Okay.
Yeah.
So when I try to import a transcript to
that particular portal Hepsi,
So he did.
I'm getting an error saying that
anthropic key, API key is not configured.
The key, right? Yeah, because,
because the reason is that I had added
the I was working on it developing,
I added the sent e-mail one,
then I put the and the key option there,
so that's the reason it's stuck there.
I then after that I didn't touch.
Yeah.
So that's why they can take it off for
now and they can do the just a standard
Okay.
way of sending or something.
Get this to working model then one thing
K.
you are you guys have to do really do use
agent to create this meeting notes if you
just.
To get the way that I have a cloud to
create, it won't create properly. OK,
so you have to have a backend agent
running and creating and putting into
here.
If you adjust to my the way that I have
it, it won't the meeting if you run.
Claude give the transcript go cloud
desktop and hey Claude can you write
create this and give me that output is
completely different than when I create
this dashboard using Claude and that
extraction is some basic thing.
So these two are not same.
That's why in order to get the same
output, I need to get the key.
But then only we talked about agent.
So the agent can run,
cloud agent can run and extract,
but and it will bring the output to the
dashboard. You guys have to do that way.
Okay.
Think about it,
we can meet another couple of days after,
maybe Wednesday or Thursday,
we can meet again and where you are and I
can help and we can discuss the next.
Anything you need more.
So they have the,
they both have the permissions to fix the
anthropic key issue, API key issue.
No, no, we cannot do that.
That's what I'm asking them to do.
The agent, Claudia agent,
create the agents to run that behind.
Okay.
And.
OK.
So just like as of now,
like the connection from our club to
teams,
this will be done by like under our team.
So like we're just gonna work on like the
outline and like the mechanisms of the
agent, not like the connecting part,
correct? Okay, let's.
Correct, correct, correct, correct,
correct. Yeah,
then we have to figure it out.
How maybe we can put it in a folder,
the if you can't directly connect,
we can have them to put it in the folder.
So then you are more like going to the
folder and take it and do run the program.
Something like that we can do it.
Alright, sounds good. Hepsi,
I'll need to request access for GitHub
just to, like, for I guess for the future,
if that's OK.
Yeah, open a case, open a case.
I will approve if it comes to,
I think it will come to me.
I will approve for that. Okay.
You have a helper next to you.
I can see Leland.
Ohh yeah, I see, yeah.
Okay, okay, okay, so sounds good.
So we'll do it and we can connect again
Thursday or Wednesday whenever you guys
wanted to have discussion to more, okay?
Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Bye bye. Bye. Bye.
Have a good Hepsi.
It sounds good. Thank you so much.
Thank you, guys. Thank you.
All right. Thank you. Bye.
Yeah, it was good.
Nice, uh,
should we like divide up like some,
is it possible to kind of like work on
one, like to work on like a shared agent,
like in a shared cloud setting?
The issue with the issue is with creating
an agent is an agent has to run on a
Mhm.
certain folder.
Reddy.
And right now we can only do it locally.
We can, we can maybe share a same GitHub.
Uh.
Mhm.
and just push the same folders,
but we'll need to update it manually
every time.
Okay,
I mean that part like we can do like if
we do have GitHub.
Yeah, I Luckey,
I need a I need a access GitHub though,
or request access do that right now.
Okay, I already have GitHub access,
so I'll try like creating our shared
folder and I'll, like for now,
like today or tomorrow,
I'll just like put in like whatever I can.
All right, wait,
do you know which GitHub you requested to
access from? There's like a lot of,
is it just GitHub automation?
Yeah.
So...
Yeah, which tile do you have?
I did GitHub engineering.
What are like the options that you have
for GitHub?
I see GitHub Automation IT,
GitHub Copilot, GitHub Engineering, CTF,
I did get I did get up engineering,
but I I think I also did get up CTO.
GitHub IT.
Hold up.
Okay.
Let's, I might.
Yeah, this is how confusing.
Repository for.
Wonder which one I need.
Maybe automation sounds about right.
I miss Gwen, thank you, that's.
I probably a W tool.
Yeah, we could, uh, Ryan,
we could open me another time just to see,
like, how we can tackle this.
Yeah.
But it's similar to like what we were
creating.
Yeah,
I think it's like a extension of like
Um...
what we were doing, right?
For GitHub.
Well,
I think Anil told me like what to do here.
I might just get the one you have,
but I'm confused because it says
engineering. Engineering users only.
Did you click on get up IT request or get
up automation suite?
Uh, I haven't clicked on any yet.
Flowered.
OK, for honesty automation, and...
Yeah, to access like the company GitHub,
I think I did the CTO thing.
OK, I'm gonna just do that.
I think Hepsi can probably just give it
to me.
Yeah.
functional area.
The key to give me all these.
So, this...
I.
Hello.
Yeah, I submit the ticket.
From GitHub CTO.
Yeah.
Nice.
Wait, why is it not working?
Okay, yeah, that's good. Okay,
just let me check.
It should be good, yeah, um...
Because we can easily create these agents
on the blog, like...
He's just like, you use prop to the agent,
and then you like connect it to some
Yeah.
folders.
Mm.
We can probably research how to make a
good one, but...
We don't have the command center access
yet, right?
No, I think she wants us to...
I guess we're just prototyping our own
agents.
Uh-huh.
And then...
Well, wait, let me go back to...
I wonder if we can make a mock-up of the
command center, like the meeting notes,
like what she had.
Mmh.
See if I can find it.
Like our, as in like our own prototype.
Yeah, here, let me share my screen. Like,
what if we...
Because, like,
this is like what she wants, right?
And then...
When you imported transcripts,
you import the transcript and then it
will...
Or, wait, Hepsi wants to automate this,
right? Instead of mainly importing it,
Yeah.
as soon as the meeting is done,
then it will like send out action items.
Is that what she wanted?
Mmh.
Yeah.
Okay.
But for that,
like we need like direct cloud access,
Hello.
like from cloud to Teams, but I don't,
that's not set yet. So yeah,
We don't have that, I think.
I think like we're just making the back
end stuff like the,
like how the engine would work and once
the connection is stable and set,
I think that's when we kind of implement
it.
Yeah,
so I think right now we'll just do
regular importing.
Mhm.
Okay, let me find...
See if I can download one of these.
For an example.
I think that.
I download this transcript.
Okay.
How are you liking school, though,
like a cow?
School are like the first people syllabus
week, so it's like been kind of chill,
but like there's like a class that's like
hella scaring me.
Lekhan.
Professors like you need you need to know
like all of these prereqs,
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
which I obviously don't know about.
So yeah.
Yeah.
It always happens.
Wait, Leland, you have one one year left,
right? Two semesters.
Yeah.
I...
A bit, a bit scary. It can,
can I please download this?
And.
Yes, yes, I ran it. Let me find that.
Maybe a gain site?
I never recorded those over here.
After I don't have access.
Bro, I'm not going to shut up.
I need to start recording my meetings.
Wait,
you're just downloading the transcripts,
right?
I'm trying to see,
but I have no access to any of these.
I will.
Yes, sir.
I'll send you one of my transcripts.
I do this all the time, so...
Yeah, perfect. Yeah, sure.
Try the same way.
I actually downloaded one.
Let me see if this works.
For a minute,
worth this small amount of data.
I think we can help answer that.
The word?
Agent.
Hello, have an error reading the file.
Little freestyle.
Brian, can you try? I'm having errors.
Or is it, or is it analyzing, Ryan? Yeah.
Should I try it on my the H channel on my
computer?
Yeah, yeah,
try importing it on your command center.
Hi.
Because it's analyzing.
Analyzing.
Yeah, I'm having cares right now.
I still analyzing.
Three.
You.
Sure.
So, Katie.
Hello.
Water requested for too much.
Oh wait, Faraz, it's still analyzing.
Wait, try again.
It might be in the air because...
Yeah, it should, it should take that long.
What's my text file?
This is kind of short, so...
Yeah, it keeps us error reading final.
Yeah, I'm doing a text file right now.
See the search.
Where is?
That's not key.